LUKE MOSELEY

Iukemoseley15@outlook.com

!ucidevz.github.io/portfolio/

GAMEPLAY PROGRAMMER

in linkedin.com/in/luke-moseley-79013a2ab

SKILLS

- C#
- C++
- Python
- UE Scripting

SOFTWARE

- Unity
- Unreal Engine
- Construct
- Visual Studio
- · Visual Studio Code
- GitHub

EDUCATION

University of Gloucestershire

(2022 - Current) -

BSc) Computer Games
Programming (Ongoing -

2nd Year)

Predicted 1st

Birmingham Ormiston Academy

(Sep 2018 - Jun 2022) -

BTEC Level 3 National Extended Diploma in Games

Design and New Media

Triple Distinction*

BTEC Level 2 TECH Award in Creative Media Production (Games Design)

Distinction*

REFERENCES

References available upon request

INTRODUCTION

A Computer Games Programming student at the University of Gloucestershire who loves to implement creative and engaging gameplay systems. Worked on solo and team projects in Unity and Unreal Engine, using C# and C++. Always enjoys opportunities to learn new concepts and develop skills, as to get a deeper understanding of how gameplay mechanics work to gain the knowledge to create a variety of different systems. Enthusiastic about bringing ideas to life to create experiences that audiences of all types can enjoy. An example being the opportunity to present "Throw your friends", a team project at COMX (the university's end of year showcase). Pursuing hands on experience of creating games within a team of talented and passionate individuals in a placement starting in summer 2024.

EXPERIENCE

Student Ambassador

Nov 2022 - present

- Represented the university at 20+ events such as open days and school visits.
- Engaged with prospective students and parents about the university and my own experiences while studying here.
- Responsible for running guided campus tours, presenting the facilities we
 have and answering questions that prospective student and families may
 ask.

Volunteer Work -

Jan 2019 - Current

- Volunteered as a leader for a local scout group (1st Walsall Wood) for 4 years. Progressed from young leader to leader.
- Helped with the planning and delivery of activities and events.

OTHER INTERESTS

- Member of scouting association for 12+ years (from 6 to 18 years old).
- Fencing at Sutton Coldfield Fencing Club, and competed in competitions (5 years).
- Participated at game design showcase events at BTEC, presenting the projects we made and giving people an idea of the work we completed on the course.
- Recreated the original Super Mario Bros. as part of a BTEC project, which is now showcased at their open events.
- Developed mobile games that I've published to itch.io.
- · Bronze and Silver DofE holder.
- Presented group project at COMX, university's end of year show, promoting our game to the general public.